bannerconnect.net 2016-11-26

# Privacy Policy - Bannerconnect

Effective Date: September 17, 2014

These privacy statements have been developed to provide website users with information on data and cookie usage;

  * Please click here for more information on how Bannerconnect uses data and cookies as part of its business that delivers digital advertising services for its clients. To opt-out of these services please click here to opt-out user from all services.
  * Please click here for more information on how information is used on this website, www.Bannerconnect.net/ (“Bannerconnect Website”). The Bannerconnect Website is operated by Bannerconnect BV.

Please note that because of the changing nature of privacy laws, user needs, and our business, we may modify these privacy statements from time to time. Accordingly, since we want to help you clearly understand our Privacy Policy and any pertinent revisions, we encourage you to review these privacy statements periodically to become aware of any changes that may have occurred. You can determine when these privacy statements were last revised by referring to the “Effective Date” above.

If you have questions or concerns regarding these privacy statements, you should contact us through email or by mail. You can address your general questions and comments by e-mail to [privacy@bannerconnect.net](mailto:privacy@bannerconnect.net "Email us") or by mail to _Bannerconnect, BV., Poststraat 12, 6135 KB, Sittard, the Netherlands Attn: Legal Department._

**Section 1: Bannerconnect Services Privacy Policy and Cookies  
**

For more information about the privacy practices of our company website and to understand how the Bannerconnect Website uses cookies and information that you may submit to us, please click here

**Bannerconnect’s Services**

Bannerconnect provides a range of services to its clients, including advertisers and publishers. Bannerconnect’s services (“Services”) include: media planning, buying and selling; marketing communications planning; campaign analytics and research; ad serving; and data management. Our clients use our Services in order to show online users the most useful and relevant ads. We believe that such advertising is a crucial element of the Internet ecosystem, providing information to users and helping to subsidize online content and services.

**Types of Information We Collect through Our Services**

When you view and interact with websites and advertisements operated by our clients, we may collect through our Services information regarding your browsing, usage and interactions. We may also collect information that allows us to identify browsers we have interacted with previously. Such information collected by our Services may include the type of Internet browser and computer operating system you use, your computer’s Internet protocol (“IP”) address, the URLs of the websites you visited before and after viewing an advertisement, and information related to websites and web pages you are viewing when an advertisement is shown.

We do not collect users’ names, mailing addresses, phone numbers, email addresses or similar personally identifiable information. Whenever we refer to “you” or “your”, we are referring to a browser or device and not an identifiable person.

We collect information through the use of cookies, pixels and similar technologies. A cookie is a small text file that is stored in a browser by a website or ad server which allows that website or ad server to recognize that browser and remember user preferences and other information. A pixel is a line of code that is used by a website or third party to assign online activities to a computer or browser. The use of a pixel allows websites and us to record, for example, that a user has visited a particular web page. Additional information from an earlier period or interaction may be included in the pixel.

**How We Use Information Collected through Our Services**

We use the information collected through our Services to provide you with the most useful and relevant online advertising and to better customize the sort of advertisements you see on those sites. For example, if we think that a user is interested in apparel options, then our Services may help our clients deliver interest-based online advertisements to you about a particular type of apparel. For example:

_Today John is looking at a mobile provider website and checking out handsets and tariffs. At the bottom of the webpage, there is a small piece of code that is used by an interest-based advertising company to log that John’s computer has visited this page._

_After visiting the page, John’s computer is assigned a unique reference number, so that we never need to know anything about John as an individual._

_When John visits a website his computer is recognised by the unique reference number. Down the side of the page, adverts appear from the mobile provider website he visited earlier. This advertsing is selected on the basis of the prior visit to that website._

We also may use such information to limit the number of times you see a particular ad, and for other purposes such as research, reporting and analysis.

We may also receive from other companies information collected outside the Services for use in connection with the Services on behalf of our clients. We also do this in order to get a clearer picture of the types of advertisements that might be most relevant and useful to you. We do not associate such information with your name, mailing address, email address or similar personally identifiable information.

We require our clients to comply with applicable laws governing online privacy. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of the websites you visit to better understand issues relating to your online privacy.

The use of information by our affiliates, clients and service providers is not covered by this privacy policy.

**Disclosure of Information to Third Parties**

We may disclose the information we collect about you (see “Types of Information We Collect through Our Services” above), and information derived from it, to our clients and service providers. As we do not collect users’ names, mailing addresses, phone numbers, email addresses or similar personally identifiable information through our Services, we do not disclose any such information to third parties. However, if you affirmatively provide personally identifiable information via one of our clients’ advertisements or websites, then that information will be received by such client and will be subject to that client’s privacy policy.

We also may disclose the information we collect to third parties, including law enforcement, when we reasonably believe we are obligated to do so by law, and in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual prohibited activities, including, but not limited to, fraud and situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person.

**User Choice**

We collect information through our Services through the use of cookies, pixels and similar technologies. We believe that the use of such technology enables us and our clients to provide users with a more meaningful web experience.

You may adjust your browser settings to refuse or remove cookies. However, by doing so, you may not be able to use certain features on the websites you visit or take full advantage of all website offerings and interest-based advertising. You may refuse or remove cookies by following the directions provided in your browser settings. Further information about cookies is available at [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/ "AboutCookies.org").

We are a member of the IAB and are referenced on Your Online Choices. [Click here](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/ "Your Online Choices") to visit their website. Select your location, by clicking on “your ad choices”, here you can opt out on cookies from specific companies.

**Digital Advertising Alliance, IAB Europe, and Ad Choices**

Bannerconnect supports deployment of the Advertising Option icon (Ad Choices) as part of its participation in the Digital Advertising Alliance’s self-regulatory framework (in North America) and the IAB Europe OBA Framework (in Europe). Advertisements that are provided by organisations that participate in these frameworks will display the icon set out below when technologically feasible. If you click on the icon displayed on an ad, you will receive information about interest-based advertising.

**Children’s Privacy**

We are sensitive to the issue of children’s privacy. Therefore, our website and Services are neither developed for, nor directed at, children or at websites primarily directed to children. If you believe a child has provided us with personal information and you would like to have the information removed, please contact us at [privacy@bannerconnect.net](mailto:privacy@bannerconnect.net "Email us").

**Linking to Other Websites**

A link from our own website to another website does not imply our endorsement of that website. We do not control the websites to which we link and assume no responsibility for their content or privacy policies. Therefore, you should carefully review the privacy policies that apply to any websites you access from our website.

**Transfer of Data upon Change of Control**

In the event that another company acquires all or substantially all of the assets of our business through a consolidation, merger, asset purchase, or other transaction, we reserve the right to transfer all information (including any information a user may have provided through the “contact us” page) that is in our possession or under our control to such acquiring party.

**Information Security**

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect against the unauthorized access to, retention of, and disclosure of data. This includes undertaking necessary physical, electronic, and management activities required to protect data integrity, access, and use. Any data that is stored on our servers is treated as confidential information. Please keep in mind, however, that despite these reasonable efforts to protect data on our servers, no method of transmission over the Internet is guaranteed to be secure. Therefore, while we strive to protect your data at all times, we cannot guarantee its absolute security and shall not be liable for any breach of security by an outside party.

**Data Retention**

We generally maintain the information we collect through our Services in non-aggregated form for a period of not more than six months. This data includes web sites visited, content viewed, ad interactions, IP addresses (please see “European Data Protection Principles” section below for additional information about IP addresses), browser type and language settings.

We may maintain information we collect through our Services in an aggregated form for a period longer than six months.

**Section 2: Bannerconnect Website Privacy Policy  
**

**How information is used and shared on the Bannerconnect Website**

We respect the privacy of users of our website.

We also recognise that when you choose to provide us with information about yourself, you trust us to act in a responsible manner with that information. This Policy contains important information about how we use your personal information collected via the Bannerconnect Website.

**What information do we collect?**

When you use the Bannerconnect Website, we may gather the following information about you:

  * IP address (a unique identifier for your computer or other device)
  * Mobile device ID
  * Information (which may include personal information such as name, address, email address, and telephone number) provided by you when you submit your CV or a job application to us or request information from us.

**How do we use it?**

We will use this information in the following ways:

  * to provide you with information that you have requested;
  * to respond to specific queries you may raise regarding Bannerconnect, its business, the services it provides to clients and any of its group companies;
  * to process and consider your CV and/or job application;

**Do we pass your information to third parties?**

We may send your information (including your personal information) to other group companies, affiliates and third parties to help us process that information for the purposes set out in this privacy statement. In addition, in the event that another company acquires all or substantially all of the assets of our business through a consolidation, merger, asset purchase, or other transaction, we reserve the right to transfer your information (including your personal information) to such acquiring party.

We also may disclose your information (including your personal information) to third parties when we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law, and in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual unlawful or otherwise prohibited activities, including, but not limited to, fraud.

**How do we use your information for marketing?**

We will only provide information to you that you have requested.

**Where do we send your information?**

We are part of a global company and therefore we may transfer your personal information to countries around the world including the US and other countries outside Europe. We will, where necessary, put in place appropriate safeguards to ensure your information is protected.

**How long do we keep your information?**

We will keep your information for a reasonable period for the purposes set out above, usually for between 12 to 18 months from the date of receipt.

**Cookies: what are cookies?**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored in a browser by a website or ad server which allows that website or ad server to recognize that browser and remember user preferences and other information. You can select which cookies are stored on your computer, by choosing to “accept” or “refuse” them. These options can be found within your browser settings.

Further information on cookies is available at [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/ "AboutCookies.org")

For more information about the specific cookies Bannerconnect uses on the Bannerconnect Website, please [click here](http://www.bannerconnect.net/cookie-declaration/ "Cookie Declaration")

**Controlling Cookies set from this Website**

This can be done as described [here](http://www.bannerconnect.net/cookie-declaration/ "Cookie Declaration")

**Third-Party Websites**

Our website links to third-party sites. These websites may use cookies and collect your personal information in accordance with their own privacy policies. This Policy does not apply to third-party websites and we are not responsible for third-party websites.

**How do we protect your information?**

We take appropriate measures to ensure that your personal information disclosed to us is kept secure, accurate and up to date and kept only for so long as is necessary for the purposes for which it is used.

**Under 13 year olds**

The Bannerconnect Website is not intended or designed to attract children under the age of 16. We do not knowingly collect personal information from or about any person under the age of 16. If You are under 16 years old and wish to ask a question or use this site in any way which requires You to submit your personal information, please get your parent or guardian to do so on your behalf.

**How to obtain a copy of your information**

You are entitled to ask for a copy of the personal information we hold about you (for which we may charge a small fee) and to have any inaccuracies in your personal information corrected. Please contact us using the details set out below.

**How to contact us if your information or choices change**

If your personal information or your preferences change, if you don’t want us to send you the information you have requested or if you have any queries about how we use your personal information, please let us know by contacting Bannerconnect at the following email address: [privacy@bannerconnect.net](mailto:privacy@bannerconnect.net "Email us")
